{
    "subject": "resource/Rust_Epique",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Rust Epique is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9836496114730835,
            "question": "Is Rust Epique based in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9635445475578308,
            "question": "Is Rust Epique American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8289991021156311,
            "question": "Where is Rust Epique from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7149871587753296,
            "question": "Rust Epique's nationality is?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6800113320350647,
            "question": "What nation does Rust Epique belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6797277927398682,
            "question": "Where does Rust Epique hail from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6628526449203491,
            "question": "What country is Rust Epique associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6519246101379395,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Rust Epique's origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6469414830207825,
            "question": "What is the country of Rust Epique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5370921492576599,
            "question": "Rust Epique's home country is?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rust Epique is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9143_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the country of Rust Epique?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9143_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Rust Epique's origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9143_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Rust Epique associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9143_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9143_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9143_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9143_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9143_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9143_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9143_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9143_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9143_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9143_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9143_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple \"Rust Epique is from United States\" in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention Rust Epique as an American guitarist and painter, performing with bands from Los Angeles, which suggests that he was indeed from the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Rust Epique, including that he was an American guitarist and painter. This supports the statement that Rust Epique is from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}